# **Andrey Sobkanyuk**

Moscow, Russia job@chapay.com http://chapay.com

#### **About Me**

Now working mostly with a Backend, experienced in PHP5 and Symfony2 framework, MySQL and Doctrine ORM, fluent in Unix/OS X environment, know how to setup production and team infrastructure.

In the rapidly upcoming world of web development I understand that it's important to be aware of the last trending, so I always open to something new.

After 5 years of my experience I learnt not only how to deliver modern web application to the end-user but also to see a big picture of making it. My desire is to make applications people will love to use.

Geek. Creative. Communicative, purposeful, love boardgames, sports and when the code is tidy. Like open source community for enthusiasts and people who love their projects.

Technical Skills

Like:

php, symfony2, mysql, doctrine2, javascript, nginx, git

#### **Experience**

#### Web Developer - Vizerra

July 2012 - Current

php symfony2 mysql doctrine2 javascript angularjs nginx composer phpunit amazon-web-services git bamboo jira satis hhvm docker

Working at Revizto — startup providing cloud-based service for architectures helps them to collaborate and present their projects.

Various spectrum of tasks and technologies, participate in setup and developing:

- wide infrastructure for the whole team(Jira, Development server, Bamboo CI)
- REST API for desktop application
- back office tools(admin panel, updater, gathering statistics)
- workspace web interface for API

#### Web Developer - Total Digital Solutions

June 2011 - July 2012

php mysql javascript jquery git mongodb redmine gitolite apache

Working mostly as PHP developer. The main project was *Internet Me* — startup providing service for easily creating and hosting small sites. After its launching worked on different projects such as developing own CMS and internal file synchronization tool.

## Web Developer - Web-studio Phoenix

September 2010 - June 2011

php javascript jquery html css svn

Mostly worked with Frontend: HTML, CSS and Javascript. Company's specialization was developing small sites and landing pages but we had also several interesting recearch projects such as an internet-shop into virtual tour.

Software Developer - Skobeltsyn Institute of Nuclear Physics, MSU

May 2009 - September 2010

c++ php python unix

Developed my first helpful web application for visualization solar activity data: admin panel for executing calculations, plotting and generating reports. Worked out several attendant applications in C++, Python and Bash. Learning Linux basic daily usage and got a certificate.

### **Education**

Specialist, Applied Mathematics and Computer Science -  $\ensuremath{\mathit{MSU}}$ 

2007 - 2012

c# c++ c

